Plan for Versions Feature:
1. Meta format change: Add 'versions' array to meta.json entry for a series.
   - Fallback if 'versions' is not present: the default folder path acts as 'Version 1'.
2. Server changes (server/index.js):
   - Modify GET /api/manga/:id to group chapters by version, or return info for the specific version chosen. Best approach is to return all versions and their respective chapters so the client can switch between them.
   - Modify Add/Edit endpoints to be able to add a version (POST /api/manga/:id/versions). 
3. UI Add/Edit Series changes:
   - Allow adding versions here. Maybe the Add Series dialog is fine, but Edit Series (or even a new 'Add Version' button inside MangaDetail) would be the place to manage them.
   - Let's add an 'Add Version' modal or just include it in MangaDetail edit modal.
4. UI MangaDetail.jsx changes:
   - Add a Versions Tab or selector near the top.
   - If selected version changes, the loaded chapters list updates.
   - Save the selected version in localStorage or logic.
5. Reader:
   - Reader needs to know which version it is reading to fetch the right chapters array, or it just reads from the chapter array passed to it.

Since the user requested: 'Di halaman Series, tambahkan Tab baru: Versions' or a selector. 

Let's do a backend update first: Add version concept to metadata.
Versions changes in server: 
1. The metadata for a manga adds an optional 'versions' array.
type Version = {
   id: string,
   name: string,
   description: string,
   type: string,
   sourcePath: string | null
}
2. Right now, mangaDir maps 1:1 to MANGA_PATH/id.
If versions are used, the 'sourcePath' or a new subfolder in MANGA_PATH/id could store the version's chapters. Or, maybe versions are just a virtual wrapper - they point to a specific folder on the user's disk (like Fan TL path vs Official path). Wait, the user said 'Add Series Version' in Add/Edit Series. This means versions are probably just alternate folderPaths or stored directly. To keep it simple, MANGA_PATH/id... no, a version could be MANGA_PATH/id/versions/version_id? But that changes the file structure a lot.
Alternatively: 
A Series entry in meta.json can define versions.
If no versions, the series uses 'MANGA_PATH/id/' as its root for chapters.
If versions are defined, each version has a 'folderPath' mapping to where its chapters are. Actually, it's easier to store the versions inside MANGA_PATH/id/version_id/ to keep them contained. But we only copy/link if they gave a folderPath.
Let's see: Add Series creates a folder: MANGA_PATH/title.
If there's a version, maybe MANGA_PATH/title/version_id?
Actually, if the user doesn't specify a folder path, we just create the subfolder. So the 'root' of a version is either MANGA_PATH/title (if no versions explicitly added, backward compatible) OR MANGA_PATH/title/versions/version_id/.
Wait, if versions exist, let's just make the app look at MANGA_PATH/title/version_id. 

Better:
In meta.json:
id: {
    versions: [
         { id: 'default', name: 'Default', chapters: [...] } (implicit)
    ]
}

Let's modify the backend to support version querying.

Wait, when 'Add Series' is used, they provide a folder path, and we just link/copy it to MANGA_PATH/dirName.
We can add a 'Add Version' endpoint: Route: POST /api/manga/:id/versions.
Body: name, description, type, folderPath.
Action: Generate an ID for the version (e.g., 'v_' + timestamp).
Save it in meta[id].versions array. 
If there's a folderPath, we can symlink it inside MANGA_PATH/id/versions/version_id ? Wait, currently we just point to it maybe?
Wait, if a series uses multiple versions, maybe the frontend needs to fetch chapters from the selected version. 
Right now GET /api/manga/:id returns all chapters for the base series.
We can update it:
meta.versions = [ { id, name, description, type, sourcePath } ]

GET /api/manga/:id
Returns:
{
  ...mangaInfo,
  versions: [
      { id: 'default', name: 'Default', chapters: [...] }, // base folder chapters if they exist, or the first version
      { id: 'v123', name: 'Official', chapters: [...] }
  ]
}

Then in MangaDetail, the user can switch.
If chapters for a version are stored in 'sourcePath', we need getChapters(sourcePath) if sourcePath exists.
Wait, if we use a direct sourcePath from outside the MANGA_PATH, how does '/api/serve/:id/:ch/:file' serve it?
Right now it serves from path.join(MANGA_PATH, id, ch, file).
If a version uses a different path, we need an endpoint '/api/serve-version/:id/:versionId/:ch/:file' that looks up the version's sourcePath or symlink location.

Actually, it's safer to always symlink the provided folderPath into MANGA_PATH/id/versionId to keep serving endpoints simple.
So:
POST /api/manga/:id/version
- Generate version_id
- Ensure MANGA_PATH/id/versions/version_id exists.
- Symlink the chosen folderPath to MANGA_PATH/id/versions/version_id.
- Save to meta.

GET /api/serve/:mangaId/versions/:versionId/:ch/:file

Let's do this!


Updating server/index.js to support Versions
Here's the plan:
Modify the meta.json to support a 'versions' array for each manga.
A version looks like:
{ id: 'v123', name: 'Official', description: '', type: 'official' }

When we call GET /api/manga/:id
We should look at m.versions. If it exists, we also return the versions.

Wait, if we use versions, how do we distinguish Chapter 1 of Base vs Chapter 1 of Version A?
If we use subfolders inside MANGA_PATH/:id/versions/:version_id/, then we can just read chapters from there.
So, a user can provide a folderPath when creating a version, which is symlinked to MANGA_PATH/:id/versions/:version_id/

Let's write a function 'getVersionChapters(mangaId, versionId)'.
If versionId is provided, we read from MANGA_PATH/:id/versions/:versionId.
If not, we read from MANGA_PATH/:id (the default).

Let's modify GET /api/manga/:id to:
- Get base chapters usually.
- For each version in m.versions, get its chapters by looking at its directory.
- Return the full structure so the client has everything.

Oh, if a series ONLY has versions (no base chapters), then we should probably just return the versions. The client can pick the first version.

First, let's update GET /api/manga/:id:

Changes to make:
1. 'versions' array in meta.js
2. Backend API to fetch a version's chapters.

Wait, if we change the backend to handle versions, what endpoints change?
GET /api/manga/:id
Returns:
{
  ...
  chapters: [...] (default chapters in base path)
  versions: [
    { id: 'xxxx', name: 'Official', description: '', type: 'tl', chapters: [...] }
  ]
}

If a version exists, the client can use it.
But how does the client fetch the images for a version chapter?
Right now: GET /api/manga/:id/:chapter -> reads from MANGA_PATH/id/chapter
If version: GET /api/manga/:id/version/:versionId/:chapter -> reads from MANGA_PATH/id/versions/versionId/chapter

And serving the image:
/api/serve/:id/versions/:versionId/:ch/:file -> path.join(MANGA_PATH, id, 'versions', versionId, ch, file)

Let's modify the server routing to support versions gracefully.

Okay, I'll update the endpoints.
1. getChapters() helper needs a path. This is already supported.
2. getCbzImages() uses mangaId and chapterFile. 
Let's refactor getCbzImages to accept a full dirPath instead of mangaId.

Actually, the easiest way to add 'version' support is by injecting a 'version' parameter into API endpoints or checking if the route starts with /version. 

Let's modify the server code directly. 
Let's update GET /api/manga/:id to also return versions.
